 const data = [
    {
      question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Router",
      option3: "LAN Cable",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
      option1: "Asia",
      option2: "Europe",
      option3: "North America",
      option4: "Africa",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
      option1: "Application Software",
      option2: "Internet",
      option3: "Operating System",
      option4: "Mouse",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
      option1: "Index Page",
      option2: "Homepage",
      option3: "Sitemap",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In which of the following states, the controversial law AFSPA had been extended for the next six months in June 2022?",
      option1: "Assam",
      option2: "Manipur",
      option3: "Mizorm",
      option4: "Nagaland",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Gorumara National Park is located in which of the following Indian state/union territory?",
      option1: "Madhya Pradesh",
      option2: "Assam",
      option3: "Odisha",
      option4: "West Bengal",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "In which of the following is a writ that is issued to Courts, Corporations, Government servants or individuals directing them to perform a public duty?",
      option1: "Writ of writ",
      option2: "Writ of Writ",
      option3: "Mandamus writ",
      option4: "Prohibition writ",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "National Milk Day is celebrated every year in India on 26 November to mark the birth anniversary of _________.",
      option1: "C Rangarajan",
      option2: "M S Swaminathan",
      option3: "Norman Borlaug",
      option4: "Dr. Verghese Kurien",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which country announced on 19th December 2021 that it will no longer censor films released in theatres?",
      option1: "India",
      option2: "Pakistan",
      option3: "UAE",
      option4: "China",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which country tops the Global Health Protection Index 2021?",
      option1: "Finland",
      option2: "USA",
      option3: "Canada",
      option4: "UK",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Nagaland State Day is celebrated every year on _________.",
      option1: "29 November",
      option2: "30 November",
      option3: "1st December",
      option4: "2nd December",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which Article is for 'Protection of interests of Minorities'?",
      option1: "Article 26",
      option2: "Article 29",
      option3: "Article 27",
      option4: "Article 30",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In which state has PM Modi inaugurated the Savra-Kuddu Hydroelectric Project?",
      option1: "Gujarat",
      option2: "Uttar Pradesh",
      option3: "Himachal Pradesh",
      option4: "Maharashtra",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The plan to transfer of power to the Indians and partition of the country was laid down in the?",
      option1: "Cabinet Mission Plan",
      option2: "Simon Commission",
      option3: "Cripps Missionap",
      option4: "The Mountbatten Plan",
      ans: 4,
    }

  ];

  export default data;